One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose!
I'll find One Piece...
and become the Pirate King!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Closely Contested Block C!
Lucy and Ucy!
Off Dressrosa's coast
The Thousand Sunny
W-Who are you?!
Be quiet!
Did you just call me a mermaid?
We didn't say that!
Boy, if she keeps using that weird power, the Sunny will get all messed up!
Putting aside Franky-san's anger, can we even turn it back?
The room that used to be the men's dormitory...
I don't know.
Anyway, we can't let Sunny get screwed up anymore!
I hope she throws her attacks this way.
Away from the ship.
Huh?
Hey, guys!
Just go and take Momonosuke away from them!
Yes, Jora-sama!
My soul is swinging! My mind is full of images!
My mind is going to erupt!
Oh, she's going to do it again!
Oh! Hello?! We're here!
Aim it over here!
Don't bother with the ship! We're over here!
Oh, it's going to explode! An image of liberty and beauty!
No!
The world should be free!
Shouldn't it?!
Damn!
She did it! We're in big trouble!
This is what beauty is!
Oh no! It's not even a ship anymore!
Oh boy, oh boy!
I'm not going to fall for your trick!
Young Master-sama ordered me to kidnap Momonosuke and hijack your ship!
Indeed, now there is no way for you
Straw Hats to escape from Dressrosa!
Dressrosa
I don't need any medical attention!
Corrida Colosseum
I'm leaving!
Mr. Ricky! We can't just let you go!
We are supposed to care for all of the competitors, including treating their injuries.
It's our job.
You let people kill each other in front of an audience!
Cut the "treatment" crap!
Your head wound hasn't stopped bleeding!
Take off your mask and let us take a look!
Don't touch my mask!
Open the exit!
Everybody, hold him down. He's badly wounded!
That's a serious wound.
You should let them treat you.
Here.
Move! I can walk by myself!
Go straight and take the stairs to the basement.
Rebecca... I'm sorry.
Inside the Colosseum
Donquixote Family waiting room
Straw Hat is participating in the tournament, Diamante.
After the match works fine.
Joker wants me to kill Straw Hat?
Doffy's too indulgent.
He's giving the man who couldn't win the tournament one more chance.
Aren't you happy, Bellamy?
Assassination is an easy task.
Finish it up before the competition's over.
Hey, Bellamy! Hang in there!
After that you will get an
executive position in the Family.
I heard you're trying to kill Lucy, Cavendish.
Bartolomeo, huh? Congrats on making it to the final.
My matter with Lucy is none of your concern.
No, that man is...
not yours to kill!
I see. You too, huh.
Because he's in the limelight!
But he is my prey.
My connection with him is much deeper.
Many people have been eliminated already!
The battle for Block C is heating up!
But even though they're all tough fighters, there is one giant warrior who is literally sticking out!
He is a warrior of the new generation from the famous giants' country Elbaf!
The strongest "Pirate Mercenary"!
His name is...
Hajrudin!
He's gigantic!
Have you ever seen a giant with a logia power?
That's what I'll become with the Flame Fruit!
I'm going to become the king of...
all giants!
With just a single blow! It was like lightning!
Who can possibly stop him?!
Whoa, and meanwhile...
there is a fighting bull running out of control,
showing no fear for all those tough contenders!
He's a killer bull who slayed 21 death row prisoners during a fight in this very Colosseum!
The Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
People call him Brutal Bull, the extraordinary cow!
And somehow, someone has managed to tame this grim reaper!
Bursting into prominence, with his cool strength, he has instantly became a crowd favorite!
Lucy!
Forward, Ucy!
I like that guy, too!
Gatz-san, you should be unbiased!
Good boy! Go, go! Take them all down!
Lucy!
Even hiding his face, he becomes popular! Straw Hat!
What a funny guy.
Go Ucy!
Oh no, they've challenged Hajrudin!
Do you wanna fight me?
Oh, crap! Run, Ucy!
Ucy!
Bull!
Lucy!
That was fast!
The difference in power was evident!
In front of the rookie from Elbaf...
the Colosseum's Grim Reaper and the unknown gladiator, Lucy, were...
G-Gatz-san!
didn't stand a chance...
Huh?
The giant has been knocked down!
That was awesome, Lucy!
You can't help getting more excited as we go on!
He came in and stirred things up in Block C!
Lucy did it again!
Let me carry you to the side of the ring, Ucy.
I believe this man still has a lot more to show!
It was obvious.
I'm astonished... I didn't expect him to be that strong.
Lucy!
Hey, hey, giant man. This is a ring.
If you wanna take a nap, find a bed!
Hajrudin's enormous body was blown away by an explosion?!
What just happened?!
No, it wasn't an explosion!
Hajrudin got eliminated, but
Block C still has many strong fighters!
It was a punch that looked like an explosion, powered by those odd-shaped shoulders!
Ideo!
The one who blew away the Giant's huge body was...
XXX Rank Boxer
Destruction Cannon Ideo
the two-time champion of the
New World Central Fighting Tournament!
Destruction Cannon Ideo!
However, that's not the only fight you want to keep an eye on!
Now, take a look!
The gang of three from the Flower Country in the far east are very unique, too!
It's no use!
There you go!
You can't protect yourself from it!
Flower Country Gang Member
13th Commander of the Happou Navy - Sai
Allowing him to manipulate the impact, The Eight-Impact Fist,
Shields and armor are useless against them!
With centuries of history, the Happou Navy is...
Flower Country Gang Member
Vice Commander of the Happou Navy - Boo
just unbeatable!
If we are able to kill you,
it's going to be almost as big as winning the prize of this competition, Chinjao!
Boy...
Flower Country Gang
12th Commander of the Happou Navy (Retired)
Go home and train yourselves more before coming back, punks!
Don Chinjao
That was Conqueror's Haki!
No wonder.
He used to be a legendary pirate worth 500 million!
There is only one man that I want to fight, don't get in my way!
Thank you, Chinjao!
There are so many nice weapons to choose from now!
Whoa!
That man didn't get beaten by Don Chinjao's Haki
And he's picking up weapons in the ring!
Bounty Hunter - Jean Ango
Jean the Bandit
He is a dark horse in this competition, Jean the Bandit!
A bounty hunter that all big-time pirates in the New World hold a grudge against!
Wait, you shithead!
Now that I found you, your time is up!
I won't forgive you for sending my partner to prison!
My bullets are weapons I've picked up.
I'm a sniper!
If that partner guy was so important to you,
you should've shown spirit like you were raiding a prison!
There was an idiot like that two years ago.
Hey! That guy has already passed out!
How long will he keep punching him?!
Hey, stop, brother! He's already knocked out!
That's enough!
I restrained the wrong person.
This bastard! He called me shrimp!
Hey, Bobby, am I a shrimp?! Huh?!
From the Mogaro Kingdom
Assassins - The Funk Brothers
No, you're not! You're a big man!
Say something, you octopus!
Brother! That's enough!
I restrained the wrong person.
If I ever hear you say it again, I'll gouge your eyes out!
Older Brother
Kelly Funk
Don't keep trying to stop me, Bobby!
Younger Brother
Bobby
But this is a competition, brother.
The Funk Brothers are so brutal!
They're assassins who are well known in the underground community!
I heard they're very powerful fighters and they've even
killed some pirates worth over 100 million!
I don't care if it's a competition or not! I'm not short!
These guys are annoying.
He's just an untrained amateur boxer.
Let's see what you've got!
Hey, shrimp!
Brother!
What?!
How weak!
I mean, maybe the Happou Navy people are too strong!
What a disappointment!
You're not a powerful fighter at all, you idiot! You fool!
Gatz-san!
You're next, younger brother!
Wait! I won't fight.
I've never gotten into a fight in my entire life!
Go to hell!
He turned his back?! These brothers are the worst!
The axe broke!
The axe was even infused with Armament Haki!
How tough is his body?!
Brother.
T-That bastard called me a shrimp.
Just put it on already, Bobby!
What's going on?!
Boo!
Boo from the Flower Country is taking quite a beating!
He's already passed out!
Who's punching him?!
Is that the wimpy younger brother Bobby?!
Or the weak older brother Kelly?!
I guess that's the older one!
He got bigger and looks like a different man!
Who did you call shrimp? Try saying it this time,
I will chew a hole in your throat!
Wow! Lucy's helmet got knocked off!
Hey, give it back!
I heard this strange story, Lucy.
I heard a pirate who's worth 400 million named Straw Hat Luffy is...
secretly fighting in this competition.
Don Chinjao is charging at something!
Garp, watch me!
I'm going to kill your grandson!
Block C! There are approximately 40 contenders remaining!
It's narrowing down to the strongest!
Who's going to be the winner?!